Embedding backend: sentence-transformers/paraphrase-multilingual-MiniLM-L12-v2
Chunker: HeadingChunker
Chunks loaded: 43 from 10 files

[1] Tôi được mượn tối đa bao nhiêu tài liệu và giữ trong bao lâu?
Gold: Undergraduate: 3 tài liệu/2 tuần; graduate: 5 tài liệu/1 tháng.
Filter: {'audience': 'student'}
English expansion: How many library items may I borrow and for how long?
Content score: 1/2 (answer marker rank: 2)
  1. score=0.033 doc_id=graduate-borrowing chunk=2
     # Library borrowing rules for graduate students Borrowing privileges: Graduate students may borrow up to 5 items at a time for up to one month per item. Books may be renewed once for two weeks. Renewa
  2. score=0.032 doc_id=undergraduate-borrowing chunk=2
     # Library borrowing rules for undergraduate students Borrowing privileges: Undergraduate students may borrow up to 3 items during two weeks per item. Books may be renewed once for one week if they are
  3. score=0.031 doc_id=graduate-borrowing chunk=0
     # Library borrowing rules for graduate students

[2] Phạt quá hạn tài liệu thường là bao nhiêu?
Gold: 20,000 VND/ngày; course-specific và thiết bị: 20,000 VND/giờ.
Filter: none
English expansion: What is the overdue fine for library materials?
Content score: 1/2 (answer marker rank: 2)
  1. score=0.032 doc_id=fines-and-damage chunk=1
     # Library fines for overdue, damage and loss Minor damage: Slightly damaged and repairable • Book covers: Markings on the inside or outside, or portions ripped off, etc. • Book pages: Markings on less
  2. score=0.031 doc_id=library-faq chunk=5
     # Library FAQ about borrowing, returning and renewing 7. What is the penalty for returning books late? The library charges an overdue fine for late payment of the borrowed items from the due date or t
  3. score=0.031 doc_id=fines-and-damage chunk=2
     # Library fines for overdue, damage and loss • An audio-visual item is rendered unable to be read by devices. • Equipment is seriously broken and unrepairable. • Books/equipment/CD-DVDs are reported l

[3] Tôi có thể gia hạn tài liệu đang quá hạn không? Điều kiện gia hạn là gì?
Gold: Gia hạn bằng nửa thời hạn gốc, chỉ khi không có người đặt trước; tài liệu quá hạn phải xử lý trực tiếp tại quầy.
Filter: none
English expansion: Can overdue library materials be renewed and what are the renewal conditions?
Content score: 2/2 (answer marker rank: 1)
  1. score=0.032 doc_id=circulation-privileges chunk=2
     # Circulation privileges and circulation regulations Note: Patrons MUST return or renew all borrowed materials before their overdue time. The renewal period is half of the original loan period. Renewa
  2. score=0.031 doc_id=graduate-borrowing chunk=2
     # Library borrowing rules for graduate students Borrowing privileges: Graduate students may borrow up to 5 items at a time for up to one month per item. Books may be renewed once for two weeks. Renewa
  3. score=0.030 doc_id=staff-borrowing chunk=0
     # Library borrowing rules for staff Borrowing Rules Return or renew before due time; overdue items can’t be renewed. Renewal period = half of the original loan, allowed only if no one else has request

[4] Làm sao để trả sách khi thư viện đóng cửa?
Gold: Dùng máy trả sách 24/7 ở cổng chính.
Filter: none
English expansion: How can I return library books when the library is closed?
Content score: 1/2 (answer marker rank: 3)
  1. score=0.032 doc_id=library-faq chunk=7
     # Library FAQ about borrowing, returning and renewing 8. What should I do if I lose or damage a library book? Lost or damaged items should be reported to the library in a timely manner. Patrons will b
  2. score=0.032 doc_id=library-faq chunk=5
     # Library FAQ about borrowing, returning and renewing 7. What is the penalty for returning books late? The library charges an overdue fine for late payment of the borrowed items from the due date or t
  3. score=0.032 doc_id=library-faq chunk=11
     # Library FAQ about borrowing, returning and renewing 11. After returning the book to the library, why do I still see it listed as overdue in my account? First, please be sure that you returned the bo

[5] Sách Course Reserve được mượn bao lâu và phải trả ở đâu?
Gold: Tối đa 2 giờ; mượn/trả tại Circulation Desk tầng 1.
Filter: none
English expansion: How long may Course Reserve books be used, and where are they returned?
Content score: 2/2 (answer marker rank: 1)
  1. score=0.033 doc_id=course-reserve chunk=1
     # Course Reserve borrowing rules Students: Physical course reserves are found at the circulation desk. Course reserves are organized by call number. You will need the call number to access course rese
  2. score=0.033 doc_id=course-reserve chunk=0
     # Course Reserve borrowing rules Your instructor uses course reserves to provide you with access to selected readings from print and electronic resources such as books, lecture notes, e-books, e-journ
  3. score=0.032 doc_id=circulation-privileges chunk=3
     # Circulation privileges and circulation regulations The loan period of 06 months will be applied for faculty who borrow textbooks for course use. However, their loaned items can be subject to recall 

=== A/B metadata filter: query 1 ===
with audience=student:
  1. graduate-borrowing score=0.033 marker=False
  2. undergraduate-borrowing score=0.032 marker=True
  3. graduate-borrowing score=0.031 marker=False
without filter:
  1. graduate-borrowing score=0.033 marker=False
  2. undergraduate-borrowing score=0.032 marker=True
  3. library-faq score=0.032 marker=False
